Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
- Ibrahim
X : @sle1i
Street-talk translation
CAPE FEAR RIVER
I'm looking for Robert Cady.
Is this seat taken?
-Yeah. ma'am.
Follow me.
That's him right there.
Max's lawyer.
Let me guess.
You were just in the neighborhood and got lost?
I'm looking for Crystal.
Is that so?
Who's that?
-Little Anna Deveraux. Mama.
What's she doing here? Do they know about Crystal?
Chill out. Don't stress.
Everything's cool.
Here's Crystal.
-There's my baby. Yep.
Here you go. sweetie. Good girl.
Just tell me where she is. and I'm out.
-Leave Crystal alone.
That girl's been fighting her demons
her whole damn life.
If you mess with her.
I promise you'll regret it.
You better bounce. lady.
Fine.
Nothing to see here.
There's nothing for you here.
I got a few things to take care of...
and then I'll catch up with you guys.
Know this girl? Crystal Cady.
-Nah.
But you know the family. right?
They live down the street.
Are you a paying customer or what?
Whatever. it doesn't even matter now.
Whiskey. Neat.
Ha. sunshine.
I heard you were looking for me.
BASED ON JOHN D. MACDONALD'S
'THE EXECUTIONERS'
BASED ON THE ‘CAPE FEAR’ FILMS
TELEPLAY BY WESLEY STRICK
AND JAMES R. WEBB
Hello?
-Hey. kiddo.
Zack? Is that you?
-Yeah. it's me.
How's it going?
Pretty good. How are you guys doing?
Taking it one day at a time.
We miss you.
I wanna go home.
I know. bud. That's gonna happen.
Soon.
Just gotta hang in there a bit longer.
Then we'll all be back home together.
Group therapy is starting.
I gotta hang up.
-Zack...
Hand over your cookie.
What?
-You're not gonna eat it. Hand it over.
Maybe I am.
-For real?
I bet you won't even eat it.
Everyone knows
she's gonna kick your ass.
She's just making you wait so me
and everyone else here can get you first.
Just hand me the damn cookie.
Drop dead.
Damn.
-Get her.
Weak-ass white girl.
She's mine.
-Shut your trap. Damn.
Stay down. Cool.
POLICE MISSED CALL
NOA 4 MESSAGES
WHERE ARE YOU? TOM AND I ARE TRYING TO
REACH YOU. WORKING ON NATALIE'S BAIL. CALL.
Noa. I'm totally fine.
This sounds mad crazy. I'm with Crystal Cady.
Look up everything you can find on her.
I'll do the same.
Tell Tom I'll make it up to him. okay?
Okay.
Well. good morning. princess.
Morning.
Hope my humble abode
was up to your standards.
I survived.
Beer?
Thanks.
Did you learn that trick
from your college girlhood friends?
Who says I learned it from them?
Maybe it was the other way around.
Maybe I taught their boyfriends
and they taught theirs.
You got a big mouth.
Where's my piece?
Stashed safely away.
So...
tell me about you and Max.
You first.
Bowden. you got a visitor.
You look super impressive.
Made any friends in here yet?
I'm low-key worried about you.
What do your fellow inmates
think of prosecutors?
They're not huge fans. right?
Or do they not know yet?
They don't know yet.
Well. they're gonna find out soon enough.
Are you just here to be annoying
or you got something useful to say?
Yeah. actually I do.
I gotta tell you something major.
Save all your Kikkoman soy sauce packets...
from the mess hall.
Cuz if you mix the soy sauce
with mayo. you get this sauce...
that makes literally any meal slap.
-Go to hell.
It's so good.
Sorry. sir.
You're gonna wanna hear this.
How's it feel. Tom?
Sitting in that spot?
You need permission
to eat. sleep. or take a dump.
You need permission for everything.
How does it feel realizing
you've completely...
lost all control and agency
to do what you want when you want?
You don't got that there. do you?
That's gotta blow.
But I'm gonna give you the chance to
be the man your family actually needs.
One of my boys is having a little
present dropped off in your cell today.
So...
a little present.
Right in your cell.
It's gonna be your saving grace.
Sounds like he totally screwed you over.
Rined your whole life.
Wrecked your family.
Classic Max.
That must've sucked.
but you must've been super into him. right?
No. duh. Like I said
about what you saw... He kissed me...
Against your will.
-Yeah. against my will.
Didn't look like it.
What about you? Why are you following him.
stalking him. snapping pics?
I feel like you're low-key obsessed with him.
I am not obsessed with him.
It's because I know Max Cady
and I know what he's up to.
That's why I got those pics.
As long as he knows I got proof
of his shady stuff. he leaves me alone.
And no. you can't see 'em.
cause they're mine.
What about Amy?
And Melissa? What'd he do to them?
I'm just saying
that when Max wants something done...
he makes sure it happens.
He makes people
do whatever he wants.
“Whatever” as in...
offing themselves?
Amy Brancato moved up to Asheville.
She got a new boo and was rebuilding her life...
and then Max showed up and that was all it took.
She came back here and ended up staying
with her stepmom again.
That's where she was when they found her.
What else you know?
I gave her a little taste. She knows
I'm gonna make her life a living hell.
I'm so lucky to have you. My little girl.
I can do more for you.
When I'm with you. You figure out how to get me out yet?
Nevaeh. you're my eyes and ears.
I need you. You can't leave yet.
You said you'd get me out soon.
-And I will.
I need one more thing.
I need you to get Natalie to spill
where her mom is.
Can you do that for me?
-Yeah.
Sweet. Awesome.
And then... you finish it.
Am I supposed to off Natalie?
For real?
Before Anna dies.
she needs to know what it feels like...
to lose a kid.
Just like me.
She gotta feel that.
Think about what she did to me.
what she did to you.
We could've had sixteen years together. Father and daughter.
Can you do that for me?
Then I'll be super proud.
And then you'll get me out of here...
right?
Right? Dad?
Yeah. I love you so much.
Bye. Love you.
-Bye.
Why'd you step in?
Same reason I save tuna from the mess hall. Savoring it for later.
Don't.
You opened up to me.
We know that was real.
That's called acting. babe.
Or'd you forget I was hooking up with your bro?
Amy's stepmom Brenda is awesome.
She had a pet raccoon for a bit.
till one of the neighbors ran it over.
Damn. Have you never driven before?
-It's no big deal.
I spun around 16 times blindfolded once. I was dared.
I was like 12 beers deep.
but still did it.
This is her place. Hope Brenda's here.
How'd you get that scar on your face?
Broke out of the psych ward
and face-planted into a doorframe.
For real?
-Yeah. Shit was intense.
I dated a guard once.
Made breaking out way easier.
What? I'm hot.
-Yeah. And completely psycho.
Yeah. well. you should know.
Did Max make you do all this stuff?
He...
he made me break into your place. dose your tea with acid...
and seduce your brother
and make him chew off his own toe.
He didn't tell me to mess with you. though. That was all me.
What does he want you to do now?
He wants me to off you.
He's not gonna stop
till your whole family is completely wrecked.
Yeah. well.
he can't get to you here.
My mom can help.
We can go to the cops.
I'm not gonna off you.
but I'm not betraying Max either.
Well. looks like nobody's home.
Brenda sometimes works at the beach shop.
We can go check it out.
Is that Amy's trailer?
Where she shot herself?
Wait. We're probably not allowed there.
It's a crime scene.
Chill. I'm just gonna peep real quick.
Man...
this feels super sketch.
Wait.
-Nah. it's cool.
The police tape's already ripped down.
MELISSA CADY FOUND
That's you. With Amy.
Were you and Amy Brancato friends?
-We knew each other.
Who's this?
The dude. With the scar. In the pic?
That one.
-We're not supposed to be here.
UNKNOWN NUMBER
Did you get my little present?
Drop dead.
Do it...
and your kids will be totally fine.
-I'm not offing myself.
Buck up.
You can't touch my kids.
-Natalie's trapped with Nevaeh...
and Zack's on the second floor
in the east wing.
For now. anyway.
That's total bullshit.
I don't wanna punish your kids
for your mistakes.
That boy's like a son to me.
And your daughter...
well. our daughter.
Listen. enough is enough. I'm giving you...
a chance to make things right.
Father to father.
Take back control. Tom.
Save Zack and Natalie.
Wouldn't your brother do the exact same thing?
Go to hell. Just drop dead. Max.
I'm gonna kill you.
I swear to God I'm gonna hunt you down and kill you.
Whatever.
Max...
told a story
about a girl named Lila...
that he seduced and messed up.
Crystal Delilah Cady.
That's your name. Was that you?
Is that kid in the photo your son?
Yours and Max's?
You don't know shit.
-What happened to him? Is he...
I put him up for adoption. What'd you think?
I didn't have my life together.
I'm not talking about this.
You ain't winning him back.
You got nothing he wants.
Wait. Can I be straight with you?
I've been here before.
I broke in...
cause Amy said Max...
would talk to her every night and she'd fall asleep listening to his voice.
So I went looking
and found recordings of them.
There're recordings?
-Yeah. all on a thumb drive.
Where are they?
-On the boat.
You gotta file those motions on time.
So get your act together...
-She's on the phone.
She's not staying locked up this weekend.
-Hey. Noa.
I'll call you back.
Hope. give us a sec.
-You sure? I...
How's it going?
What do you want. Max?
-A friend. honestly.
Cause I thought Anna regretted
having me locked up. And Tom too.
But nope. they tried to frame me. And honestly? I don't get it.
So you're here looking for some sympathy?
-Yeah. Pretty much.
Cause I...
I'm trying to figure out...
Do you think maybe...
Nah. never mind.
What?
-No. do you think maybe...
Anna didn't even know what Tom was up to?
That would actually make me feel a lot better.
Do you think that's true?
Let me guess.
You want to know where she is
so you can go ask her yourself?
Yeah. That would be ideal. Noa. yeah.
Do you think I'm stupid enough
to tell you where she is?
I was stupid enough
to let you into our lives...
so you could murder my friend Ray and terrorize my friend Anna.
I'm gonna kick myself over that till the day I die.
but I see right through you now.
I'm not scared of you.
I've gone toe-to-toe with the state of Georgia and the U.S. government...
and I can definitely handle Max Cady's lame ass.
I missed that. Can I get the address where Anna is?
Where the hell is Anna?
Noa?
Actually. whatever.
Catch you later.
You're looking fire.
Thanks.
Oak Grove Psychiatric Hospital.
-Tom Bowden here. I'm trying to—
One sec. I'll grab him.
Mr. Bowden? Hello. We've been trying to get a hold of you and your wife.
There's been an incident.
What kind of incident?
I need to talk to my son.
Yeah. I'm not totally sure how. but he slipped past security...
and we haven't been able to find him anywhere nearby.
Maybe someone gave him a ride or he had help—
You absolute idiot.
-If this—
He's got my son.
CALLING...
BATTERY 5%
Jared. hit me back. Zack's missing. I think Max took him.
Let me know if Natalie's safe. okay?
Call me back. My phone's about to die.
As soon as you hear this. Noa.
By any means necessary.
Leave a message after the beep.
It's me.
I don't know where you are...
or where the kids are.
I love you.
Your girl is free.
No. Natalie.
What'd you do?
Wait. what'd you do?
Wait. Don't leave.
Don't leave. Wait. Drop dead.
So where are these recordings then?
Right there. You gotta pop the hatch open.
It's kind of heavy. but...
And then. yeah. Like that. yeah.
There's a few boxes. Pretty sure it's the one on the bottom right.
Can't you just point it out?
-You scared of tight spaces?
I know. It's—
-Nah. I just need you to show me.
Okay.
Looking for this?
Why were you wearing Melissa's necklace?
What necklace?
-Come on.
No clue...
-I saw you rocking it.
What did you do?
-I dunno.
Did you off her?
Did you murder Melissa?
I totally get it.
For real. I mean. he was so good to her.
And you were just...
trash.
She didn't deserve that life.
So?
Get down in the hold.
Anna.
Hello. Where are you?
I know you didn't kill Melissa. You didn't murder your wife.
That's right.
Amy Brancato iced Melissa. yeah.
I know you made Amy confess. but not because you were guilty.
Okay.
So who actually killed Melissa?
Crystal.
No. Crystal was locked up in a psych ward.
-Nah. A guard let Crystal walk.
I can prove it. And I've got Crystal.
Crystal was knocked up with your kid and saw you playing happy family with Melissa.
And she totally snapped.
-Wait. What?
What'd you just say?
Crystal was pregnant with my kid?
Yeah. with your baby.
The kid she claimed she put up for adoption. No clue what she told you...
but Crystal gave birth to a son.
He's gotta be out there somewhere.
I'm sure you can track him down.
I'll text you the address
of some public spot so we can talk.
And then you're gonna leave me alone.
You hear me?
You're gonna leave me and my family the hell alone.
We didn't do any of this to you.
Fine. Just send me the address.
MAX. CRYSTAL. WHAT THE HELL IS THIS?
MAKE SURE YOU GOT HER WHEN I GET THERE
Is that your master plan? Handing me over to Max?
So he'll want you back?
He wants you way more than me.
you toxic bitch.
Move.
Now what. Crys? How many times
do I gotta bail you out of your messes?
I've got a plan. Shove her in the hold.
No.
-Move.
Throw her in. You gotta roll.
-Let's talk.
Shut it.
Get out of here.
What were you gonna do if we hadn't shown up? Bash her over the head?
Leave me alone.
BATTERY 1%
Don't hurt my son.
Tom. untie yourself.
I need some air.
I can barely breathe down here.
Please?
-Ma'am?
Whatever the Cadys promised you.
it ain't worth it.
Watch what happens
if you keep running your mouth.
Luke. do you want to spend the rest of your life locked up?
It'd be a lot simpler if you just shut your trap. lady.
Oh. my god.
You good?
-Yeah. I'm fine.
I've seen that scar before.
In your baby pictures.
What?
Does Max know you're his kid?
-That's total bullshit.
I'm Crystal's kid.
-True. You're lying. bitch.
Max Cady is your dad. Luke.
-She's lying.
Shut up.
Total BS.
-Why'd you say that?
She's tripping.
-That bitch is lying.
Max is my mom's brother.
-Yeah.
Damn it.
-That bitch is lying. Shut her up. Luke.
Yeah. but what about my dad?
-Your dad is who I said he was.
He's a loser who bailed.
-She's lying. Can't you tell? Just look.
Don't let her lie to you.
-It's how I said. Crys.
The sins of the daughter
come back on the whole family.
You're stressing yourself out. I can see it.
-Chill out. kid. or you're going in the cage.
Am I going back in the cage?
To hell with your cage.
Don't talk to your grandpa like that.
-Spit it out. Mom.
I love you. I wouldn't hurt you.
-Don't...
Don't say that.
-I would never hurt you.
She's a stranger. I'm your mom.
-Spit it out.
She can't handle the truth.
She's gaslighting herself.
Shut your trap.
Mom.
Shut up.
Drop dead. asshole.
I hate you guys.
-Stop.
You're gonna kill him.
-Let go.
You lied to me.
-Stop.
Don't.
-Why'd you lie?
Drop dead.
Why'd you lie to me?
Stop. you're killing him.
-Let go.
You're gonna kill him.
Chill.
-What am I even doing here?
I wanna die. You're a trash mom.
-Relax.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm